[Music]
four things to prepare to achieve
Freedom at 50 Financial Independence
does not mean owning a large amount of
assets but having enough money to take
care of yourself pursue your interests
and prepare for unexpected
situations in fact many people when
retiring are reluctant to go for regular
medical checkups limit spending money on
personal interests such as traveling
entertainment eating out Etc improve
mental health some people after the age
of 50 gradually lose motivation in life
they gradually lose interest in daily
activities even things they used to love
some people even want to give up or
Escape reality maintain physical health
after the age of 50 most people's
physical condition will decline in women
the condition of weight and the
consequences of childbirth will be more
obvious especially after the decline of
hormones due to
menopause in men bad habits that are
maintained for many years of work such
as abusing alcohol beer and cigarettes
cause diseases related to the heart
liver lungs and kidneys to appear more
often balance
relationships the age of 50 is also the
time when most children have grown up
and started their own families Discord
between parents and children is
inevitable due to different thoughts and
life Concepts according to sociologists
instead of considering children as the
top priority in middle age each person
person needs to take care of themselves
more journalist Tran thuha a famous
person in raising independent children
shared teaching children to be
independent is also a way to help
yourself be free in addition each person
should also maintain and create social
relationships participate in groups with
similar interests and volunteer
organizations to help improve emotions